webring.com 2001-12-18

# Yahoo! Privacy

|   |  [](https://www.truste.org/validate/361) Yahoo! takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. Also, please read our [Children's Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/kids/details.html) to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable information collected from children and [Privacy Information](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/fininfo/details.html) to learn how we treat such information collected in connection with Yahoo! financial products and services.

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/sitesee/index.html) for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.**

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  

  * This Privacy Policy covers Yahoo!'s treatment of personally identifiable information that Yahoo! collects when you are on the Yahoo! site, and when you use Yahoo!'s services. This policy also covers Yahoo!'s treatment of any personally identifiable information that Yahoo!'s business partners share with Yahoo! or that Yahoo! may collect on a partner's site. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Yahoo! does not own or control, or to people that Yahoo! does not employ or manage. In addition, this policy does not apply to [Yahoo! NetRoadshow](http://www.netroadshow.com/), which has its own privacy policy, or to Yahoo! financial products and services, which are covered by [Privacy Information](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/fininfo/details.html).

**Information Collection and Use**  

  * Yahoo! collects personally identifiable information when you register for a Yahoo! account, when you use certain Yahoo! products or services, when you visit Yahoo! pages, and when you enter [ promotions or sweepstakes](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/promo/details.html). Yahoo! may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with Yahoo!, we ask for your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Yahoo! and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Yahoo! also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your [IP address](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/ip/details.html), Yahoo! [cookie](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/cookies/details.html) information and the page you requested. 
  * Yahoo! uses information for three general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  

  * Yahoo! will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. 
  * Yahoo! may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Yahoo! to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.); 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or 
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the [Yahoo! Terms of Service](http://docs.yahoo.com/info/terms/), the [Yahoo! GeoCities Terms of Service](http://docs.yahoo.com/info/terms/geoterms.html), or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Cookies**  

  * Yahoo! may set and access Yahoo! [cookies](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/cookies/details.html) on your computer. 
  * Yahoo! allows [other companies](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/adservers/details.html) that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Yahoo!'s cookies. 
  * Yahoo! uses [web beacons](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/pixels/details.html) to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Yahoo! products and services.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  

  * Yahoo! gives you the ability to edit your [Yahoo! Account Information](http://edit.yahoo.com/config/eval_profile) and preferences at any time, including whether you want Yahoo! to contact you about specials and new products. 
  * You may request deletion of your Yahoo! account by visiting our [Account Deletion](https://edit.yahoo.com/config/delete_user) page, verifying your password once more and confirming your choice to terminate the account. Please [click here](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/archives/details.html) to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**Security**  

  * Your Yahoo! Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. 
  * In certain areas Yahoo! uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  

  * Yahoo! may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. 

**Questions or Suggestions**  

  * If you have questions or suggestions complete a [feedback form](http://add.yahoo.com/fast/help/us/privacy/cgi_feedback?radio30=radio305). 
  * [Yahoo! is TRUSTe-certified](https://www.truste.org/validate/361). This certification applies to all English-language sites under the Yahoo.com domain. If you feel that your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/watchdog.html), an independent privacy organization. 

---|---|---
